>> Brian Holt: 这将 >> Brian Holt: 此处的详细信息。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: That's going to
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Details here.
我想在这里说的第一件事就是通知细节没有概念
Well, first thing I wanted to call out
here is notice the details has no concept
装的是懒惰的对吧
that it's being lazily loaded, right?
我只是写了一个正常的细节
I just wrote a normal details component.
我没有修改里面的东西让它很懒惰
I didn't modify anything inside
of this to make it lazily loaded.
它完全不知道它是如何装载的
It's blissfully unaware
of how it is loaded.
这也很酷，我不需要修改任何细节。
So that's pretty cool as well, I didn't
have to modify anything in details.
但让我们假设第二个
But let's just assume for a second that
我在这里说 import_from 'lodash' 和
here I say import_from 'lodash' and
让我们从现在开始
let's import moment as well from moment.
这些是两个相当大的图书馆，对吧 ?
So these are two pretty big libraries,
right?
在这里我们可以说我们用了它们
And here, just so
that we can say we used them,
我们会说 console.log(_ 时刻)。
we'll say console.log(_ moment).
> > Brian Holt: 现在是时候了，对吧 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: It is called moment, right?
>> 扬声器 2: 瞬间。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: moment.js.
>> Brian Holt: 瞬间?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: moment.js?
>> Brian Holt: 我们进行检查。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Let's check.
我只选择两个幼崽我知道它们比较大
I just choose those two cuz I
know that they're relatively big.
> > Brian Holt: 不，是这个。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: No, it's this one.
> > Brian Holt: 所以它很快就会开始安装。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So it's gonna go and
install those really quickly.
>> Brian Holt: 但请注意 :
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: But notice that lodash and
现在不是另一个捆绑软件的一部分吧
moment are not a part of the other bundle,
right?
他们不是 SearchParams 的一部分什么的
They're not a part of SearchParams or
anything like that,
细节都是独一无二的
they're unique to details.
所以包裹是很聪明的说
So parcel is smart enough to say, hey,
我知道这永远不会被加载到另一个捆绑软件中
I know that this is never gonna
be loaded in the other bundle, so
我可以把它包括在这个捆绑软件中， >> Brian Holt: 好吗 ?
I can just include it in this bundle,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay?
>> Brian Holt: 那么现在如果我刷新页面，请注意，此捆绑软件具有很大的内容，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So now if I refresh the
page, notice that this bundle got huge,
现在是 747 千字节
right now it's 747 kilobytes.
你可以看到这两个东西正在被加载
And you can see that there were loading
out these two things are logging
好吧
out rather.
>> 布莱恩 - 霍尔特: 所以你不用加载所有时间，不要加载所有冲刺。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So one don't load all of
moment and don't load all the lodash,
我想这可能是我的意思
I think that might be my point.
但除了这一点你想把你的工作
But besides that point, you wanna
find like heavy points to split your
如果你没有刮掉大量的
application and if you're not
shaving off a significant amount,
更糟糕的用户体验必须等待，对吗 ?
it's a worse user experience
having to wait, right?
所以这是一个你应该使用的工具，但是你应该小心使用它。
So it's a tool that you should use, but
you should be careful where you use it.
>> Brian Holt: 因此，我们也可以在这里继续使用应用，并且
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So we can go back
over to App here as well, and
我们也能用 SearchParams 做同样的事
we can do the exact same thing
with SearchParams as well.
> > Brian Holt: 现在注意，我没有更改暂挂，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Now notice
I didn't change Suspense,
我们在这里用同样的暂记东西对吧
we're using the same Suspense thing here,
right?
但如果我刷新页面，请注意，如果您转至 " 网络" ，
But if I refresh the page,
now notice that if you go to Network,
SearchParams 也是它自己的捆绑软件，对吧 ?
SearchParams is its own bundle as well,
right?
所以， SearchParams，然后我去另一个，它会加载这个。
So SearchParams, and then I go to
the other one, and it'll load this one.
但是你知道什么很酷吗
But hey, you know what's cool?
如果我回去，现在就到另一个，注意不要再装了，对吧 ?
If I go back, now, to the other one,
notice it doesn't load it again, right?
它已经拥有它，所以它能够立即执行它。
It already has it so
it is able to just instantly execute that.
所以你只会打一次
So, you'll only take that
performance hit once.
> > 布莱恩 - 霍尔特: 你可以在任何地方
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And
you can do this anywhere,
不需要只是在路上，我们可以详细了解一下，对吧 ?
it doesn't have to just be on a route,
we could go into details, right?
注意我们在这里装载模型
And notice we're loading model up here,
but
我们不需要莫达尔的正前方我们只需要莫达尔才能点击
we don't actually need Modal up front
right we only need Modal to click on it.
这样我们就能摆脱这个
So we could get rid of this and
say const Modal=lazy import./Modal.
>> Brian Holt: 对，因为莫达尔不是最初使用的，对吧 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Right, because the Modal
is not initially used, right?
莫达尔只会在 showModal 发生时使用，对吗 ?
The Modal is only used if
showModal happens, right?
所以现在如果我把这个保存在这里然后我去一个动物的网页
So now if I save this and go back over
here, and I go to one of the animal pages
>> Brian Holt: 不知道我做了什么。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Not sure what I did there.
是啊你得从 React中导入懒惰的
Yeah, you need to import
lazy as well from React,
这才是真正的功能
cuz that's needs to be a real function.
所以我被告知， >> Brian Holt:
So I'm told,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And
从现在起就可以了
then from there now this works.
现在，如果您进入网络，请注意，我们已装入应用程序，但已装入详细信息，但
Now if you go into network, notice we've
loaded app we've loaded details but
如果我在这里通过我们也会得到莫达尔
if I click Adopt here,
we get Modal there as well.
这也挺酷的
Which is pretty cool as well.
这使得代码在这些地方上分裂很简单
It makes code splitting on
these places really simple, but
更糟糕的是只有 10 千字节，对吧 ?
this is even worse this is
only 10 kilobytes, right?
因为它不是那么多的 JavaScript。
Because it's not that much JavaScript.
但为了让你觉得你可以在图书馆里分家
But just to show you like
you can split on libraries,
你也可以把一堆东西都拆了它不只是在航线上
you can split on a bunch of stuff as well,
it doesn't just have to be on routes.
>> 布莱恩 - 霍尔特: 还有一件很酷的事情，那是值得的。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And the other thing that's
cool as well, that's worth calling out.
我也没在任何地方放新的悬念组件
Notice I didn't put a new Suspense
component anywhere either,
它还在用这个顶级的
it's still using this
top level one up here.
所以您可以在不同位置有不同的暂记组件，也可以
So you can have different Suspense
components in different places, or you can
最重要的是你要如何设计你的应用
one top level one as well, that's up to
you and how you wanna design your app.